to me being 24 represents a significant
life milestone
to some it marks the end of youth
while others see it as the beginning of
early adulthood
it is the time to be assertive bold and
confident
and at the same time ever so curious
about what is ahead
what if we get to choose what we want
we can decide what and how it is going
to be like
introducing manulife universal saver a
solution that empowers you to customize
your plan according to your life goals
whatever our goals in life may be in the
next 20 years or longer we should always
have a proper financial plan in place
so i choose to plan one step ahead
more flexibility for you to begin with
relatively short-term commitment
the earlier you start saving the sooner
you can achieve your goals
you can create a financial nest egg with
potential upside and get insurance
protection against the uncertainties of
life at the same time
and should the worst happen your loved
ones are shielded from financial burden
lay the right foundation and start
planning today
no medical and financial underwriting is
required terms and conditions apply
[Music]
at age 24 i made the choice
what about you
[Music]
find out more by calling our customer
caroline or get in touch with our
manulife advisor today